

Rupesh Mandal

Android app & Java Spring boot Developer

CONTACT

- +9779821718720
- mandalrupesh883@gmail.co
- Sirha, Lahan , Lahan
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rupesh-mandal-551ab6209
- https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal
- https://twitter.com/RupeshM 17078778

SKILLS

- Java Expert
- Android app development Expert
- Android Studio Expert
- Spring Boot Expert
- API Expert
- sql Experienced
- Kotlin Skillful
- Junit Expert
- Jooq Expert
- Git Expert
- Micro service Expert

LANGUAGE

English - Experienced

SUMMARY

Hello, I am a Full Stack developer using (Java backend development with spring boot, Android app development, and Android Studio. I have more than 5+ years of experience in Software development. My Upwork profile link https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01371b669da89b56a0

EDUCATION

Bachelor of technology

Kathmandu University / Kathmandu / October, 2015 - October, 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Android app developer with Java

King world wide courier / Mumbai, India / July, 2020 - April, 2022

Android app & Java spring boot developer

SysQuo Innovation Private Limited / Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India / July, 2022 - Present

PROJECTS INVOLVED

Food Delivery App - Full Stack

https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal/foodkali_spring_boot

Ecommerce App - Full Stack

https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal/Shooply_android

Blog App - Full Stack

https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal/Blog-App-Backend

Photo Editor - Android app

https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal/Vivid-Cooleditor

Health fitness - Android app

https://github.com/Rupesh-Mandal/Health-fitnessplus

King Worldwide Courie - Full Stack Development with Android Studio + Java & Spring

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.king.worldwidecourier

Friends Dhaba - Online Food Delivery Mobile App Development with Android Studio + Java

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.billzen

International Medical Centre (My IMC) Android app with Java

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=sa.med.imc.myimc

Hindi - Expert

Nepali - Expert